One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Nico Robin is steadily
approaching the Gates of Justice...
while we're here fighting like this.
Or maybe I should say that from
her perspective, she's approaching hell?
Yeah, I know.
It's true.
Robin-chan's life is at stake!
But if you get in my way,
I won't go easy on you
just because you're a woman!
Hand over that key
before you get hurt!
Raising your voice won't yield the key.
You don't have to treat me like a woman.
I don't live in such a delicate world.
Since we've got an extermination order,
I'll just take your life,
that's all.
You can't have it.
I just want...
the key to Robin-chan's handcuffs.
Then I guess teatime is over?
Shave!
Your power is indeed
that of a superhuman.
An opening!
I landed a blow.
Hey! How could you?!
Isn't that what you call
“landing a blow”?
How dare you...? You little...
Moon Walk!
He's fast!
I've just stomped you.
That means you lost!
Now, give me the key...
Finger Pistol!
Tempest Kick!
What a disappointing man.
You're a pirate,
and yet, you're quite the coward!
Hey, shut up!
Give me the key!
I've had enough of your
transparent threats.
Shall we try something fun?
You're dead unless you fight back.
Mr. Chivalry
He's not coming after me.
First Floor - Receiving Area
Nami vs. Kumadori
Good!
If I'd have been caught again,
I'd be dead.
I'll just run and...
Life Return!
Oh, shoot!
Now, shall I...
pierce you to death...
or choke you to death?!
A wintry blast blows through this world.
Your peaceful rest comes before the first buds of spring.
At least once more,
you shall bloom lovely scarlet petals...
before you fall!
My duty is to offer such compassion!
When you arrive in the afterlife,
please tell my late mother...
that I'm... I'm doing fine...
as an assassin!
Now, die!
Now... Now... Now!
No!
Song of Spring Spirit!
Cloven Roseo!
Nami! Are you okay?!
Chopper,
Thanks. You saved me.
What's with that guy?
Does he have a devil fruit power?
I don't know.
His hair moves like an octopus,
so I couldn't do anything.
More importantly,
now is our chance, Chopper.
Let's get out of here right away.
Why?!
Unless we defeat him,
we can't get the key.
You mean this, right?
I stole the key without him noticing,
but I just couldn't get away from him.
Do you know what's going on
with the others?
Say, Nami.
What number does it have on it?
Number?
It says 3.
Wrong one.
What is this number?
Something fell down!
Is it... a doll?!
No.
Sanji!
Why does he look like this?!
Hey! What happened?!
Why is your body like this?!
Are you okay, Sanji-kun?!
Sanji!
Sorry, I lost.
I couldn't get the key.
Hold on a sec, Sanji.
I'll give you first aid.
I never thought that Sanji-kun
would lose.
Sanji-kun,
Were you really
not able to defeat her?
Did you give her an honest fight?
It was that woman who
you fought, wasn't it?
You're soft with women.
I'm sorry about the key.
That's not it!
I'm saying that because
of that stupid chivalry,
you could die!
You're gonna stick to it even
after getting hurt like this?!
What would we do without you?!
It's not like...
I want to die.
It's just that,
I was raised with the idea that kicking women is wrong beaten into me.
So,
even at the cost of my life,
I won't kick a woman!
You're an idiot.
Stupid!
Hey! What're you doing, Nami?!
If running away also violates your code of chivalry,
at least ditch that part of it!
It's not worth dying in vain.
Leave that woman to me.
Also,
I think a little more of your
code of chivalry than I did before.
What?!
Did she just say
that she loves me more?
No, she didn't!
I'm not kind.
Neither am I.
Sounds like we can get along.
Hold it!
The octopus guy!
I won't...
I won't let you get away!
Nami, you go deal with that woman!
I'll do something about this guy!
Okay!
Are you getting in my way?!
Cloven...
Cross!
Whoa! Pirate guy!
What're you doing?!
Seriously, there's no way you can cross
water like this on a boat, now is there?
Are you an idiot?!
But Robin was taken to those gates!
Unless I hurry up, I won't
be able to bring her back!
Wait, pirate guy!
Calm down!
We came to tell you how to
get to the Gates of Justice!
What?
Anyhow, you're amazing.
I'm impressed that you knew
about a passage like this!
I saw Lucci's lackey going down
the stairs, laughing very loudly.
So I followed them.
Box reads “The Lackey”
If they don't know where the entrance is,
they can't come after us!
Serves them right!
Lucci and that black-haired lady
went through the doors, too.
So these are them, huh?
They're really heavy-duty iron doors.
Do you know how to open them?
The lackey was doing something over here,
so I bet you can control
them with this keyhole!
We don't have the key, though.
You guys, step back.
Huh? What're you gonna do?
We can go to the Gates of
Justice through here, right?
Er... Yeah.
Gear Third!
They opened!
All right! I'm heading there now!
What?! How come you're small now?!
That pirate guy sure is interesting!
I-I just heard a loud noise.
Was that my imagination?
No, it couldn't have been.
Could that noise have been one of
the pirates destroying the doors?
What?! Such a ridiculous idea isn't possible!
Those are thick iron doors!
Besides, there's no way that
they could find those doors!
Well, they should know where they are,
since a child and her pet were following us.
What?!
I-If you knew that,
why didn't you kill them?!
Because...
I received no such order.
What?! You dimwit!
For something so trivial,
use your own discretion!
Couldn't you imagine what'd happen if
you didn't do anything about it?!
So what're you saying?!
Are you saying that
someone's headed this way?!
All right! Back to normal!
Just wait, Robin!
I'll be sure to beat the crap
out of that pigeon guy!
Pantry Front Passage
Franky vs. Fukuro
Dammit! I need to refill
my cola as soon as possible.
For someone with such a large body,
he sure does like to bounce around.
I'm right here.
Seems like you're at least quick
when it comes to escaping.
I'm under no obligation to take
the punches you're so proud of.
Franky Triangle Jacker!
No way...
I'd get hit by sideburns like that!
I've got you!
Weapons Left!
Seems like I'm almost out of cola.
I'd better get to the kitchen now!
Hold it!
Dammit! He dodged my attack!
Damn wimp, you're an
expert at running away!
What'd you say?!
What's the matter, wimp?
You're not running away this time?
You bastard!
You made me mad with what you said!
Take my killer fist!
It's a super heavy punch combined
with Finger Pistol's speed!
Tough Dugong!
What a puny, ineffective punch!
Strong...
Iron Body!
Hammer!
That was a pathetic punch.
Tough Dugong!
Your punches are flabby.
No.
Your punches are limp.
Then, your punches are flimsy.
Your underpants are lazy.
Underpants?
They're not punches!
Underpants! That's what you are!
You damn bra!
Shut up, socks!
Long johns!
Loose shorts!
Loincloth!
Get off of me, you bastard!
Shut up, coin purse!
Great!
I made it into the kitchen!
There it is! A huge refrigerator!
Is that him?
He probably has a gorilla-type devil fruit power.
Dammit!
Three minutes have already passed?
I used the rumble ball too soon.
What am I gonna do?
Depart the three planes of existence!
Your life ends here!
You bastard!
Good! It's got a lock!
Kumadori!
All right! I locked him in!
How dare you?!
Hey, hold on a sec, gorilla!
I need that fridge!
Ahh! CP9 and the punk!
I'm Franky! I'm on your side, remember?!
Who'd you call a gorilla?!
You're too slow!
Listen.
Just like Luffy,
I haven't forgiven you yet.
The reason Usopp left us was...
It's all your fault!
Give us Usopp back!
Like I said, you guys
were with him earlier.
That's not important right now!
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
I do! Robin!
Then get three bottles of cola from
that fridge and give them to me!
With cola, I can power up!
I'll take care of these guys in
an instant and take their keys!
What kind of idiot actually
gets stronger with cola?
Shut up! That'd be me!
Just how long...
are you planning to
keep up the comedy act?!
On top of that, you're trying to
have a tea break during a fight?
How rude!
Tough Dugong Esoterica:
Owl Thrashing!
Beans Left!
What was that?!
Ahh! This is terrible!
That's right!
He's on our side right now!
I'll do what he told me to.
If I open the door and close it in less than a second, he can't come out!
The door has...
All right!
Franky!
You're a lifesaver!
Fresh!
What the...?
Freshness is most important!
Vegetable Punch! Take this!
Tough Dugong.
Hey! That was vegetable juice!
Who's prioritizing health around here, you bastard?!
Give me cola!
Oh, so it wasn't because he was thirsty.
The door...
Here you go!
Thanks!
I'm feeling good!
Well,
let me take a rest.
My work in
the field is done for now.
Stop being so upset.
Don't fight.
Why don't you have some tea?
Tea wouldn't...
give me energy! You moron!
He's... funny.
Hey!
What's with that “I wonder what
happens with other drinks” look?!
This'll be the last time, you damn deer!
So it doesn't depend
on how you're feeling?
I need only cola!
That's it! Without a doubt!
Thanks!
I don't know what the deal is,
but I'm not gonna let you have your way!
Tempest Kick!
Franky!
Super!
What's the deal?
It's not like drinking cola would
make a difference or anything.
Put up your guard.
What a fool.
Are you gonna give me
another pathetic punch?
Strong... Hammer!
Whoooa! Amazing!
Sorry.
My punches earlier were...
indeed pathetic.